CLEL Video Oral History Project 6207 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
CLEL Video Oral History Project
2000-2018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
College of Labor and Employment Lawyers (CLEL)
Wan, Susan
Rosenbaum, Carol
6207 OH
14.11 cubic feet
14.1 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genres), audiovisual materials, transcripts.
Collection consists of digital DVD's, DigiBeta, and VHS, Beta tapes of interviews and transcripts for most of the interviews.
6018721
Biographical / Historical
The College of Labor and Employment Lawyers was founded in 1995 with a vision to recognize the profession, in all its aspects, as one uniquely important to modern economic life, individual rights, collective bargaining and dispute resolution. Established through an initiative of the Council of the Section of Labor and Employment Law of the American Bar Association, the College operates as a freestanding organization recognizing those who have distinguished themselves as leaders in the field through sustained and outstanding service.
The College is managed by its officers and a Board of Governors. The sixteen-member Board of Governors is composed of an equal number of Fellows from four constituencies: those who have primarily represented organized labor, employers, plaintiffs, and those serving as neutrals, whether in government, in academia, or as mediators and arbitrators. This structure is designed to bring every part of the profession together to further excellence and integrity in the profession. Fellows are nominated exclusively by other Fellows and elected by the Board of Governors after due diligence has established that a nominee meets the highest standards of the profession. There are three categories of Fellows: Fellow, those in active practice, Fellow Emeritus, those who are retired; and Honorary Fellow, reserved to sitting judges and outstanding individuals who have made substantial contributions to the field but are not lawyers. The College functions entirely within the profession. It is forbidden by its Bylaws from taking legislative positions.
Scope and Contents
The Video History Project's primary purpose is to create a repository of oral histories documenting significant employment law topics or events. By videotaping distinguished individuals who played a significant role or who had an opportunity to observe a milestone event, the project can protect the past and serve the future. Subjects include: WJ Usery (former Secretary of Labor); UW Clemon (the first African American Chief Judge, US District Court for the Northern District of Alabama); Theodore Kheel (one of New York's most influential public advocates); Willard Wirtz (former Secretary of Labor); George Nicolau (nationally recognized labor arbitrator); Max Zimny (former General Counsel, ILGWU and UNITE!); Paul Tobias (founder of the National Employment Lawyers Association); John Truesdale (former Executive Secretary and Chairman of the NLRB); Howard Jenkins (first African-American Member of the NLRB); Arvid Anderson (distinguished public sector arbitrator and Chair of the New York City Office of Collective Bargaining); Sam Pointer (former Chief Judge, US District Court for the Northern District of Alabama); Don Banta and Warren Sullivan (distinguished Management lawyers with over fifty years of experience); Betty Southard Murphy (the only person to have served as both Chairman of the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) and as Administrator, Wage and Hour Division); and Marvin Miller (former Executive Director of the Major League Baseball Players Association).
Collection consists of digital DVD's, DigiBeta, and VHS, Beta tapes of interviews and transcripts for most of the interviews.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6194 OH: College of Labor and Employment Lawyers Interview with Theodore W. Kheel
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 11, 2019
Oral history; Anderson, Arvid (Arvid Asa), 1930-; Atwood, Cindy; Bairstow, Frances K.; Banta, Don; Brown, William H., III; Cashdan, David; Cohen, George; Clair, Edward; Clemon, U. W., 1943-; Cummings, Frank; Elisburg, Don; Ginsberg, Ruth Bader; Gombar, Bob; Gottesman, Mike; Harkless, James; Higgins, John E.; Hough, Les; Jenkins, Howard, 1915-; Kearney, Barry; Kheel, Theodore Woodrow; Kilberg, William J.; King, Patricia; McAteer, Davitt; Miller, Marvin; Mintz, Ben; Moffett, Kenneth E.; Moure-Eraso, Rafael; Murphy, Betty; Nagle, Bob; Nicolau, George; Orza, Gene; Outten, Wayne; Pointer, Samuel C., Jr.; Rabinowitz, Randi; Railton, Scott; Robinson, William L.; Rogers, Thomasina; Rose, Henry; Sacher, Steve; Sachsel, Allen; Salem, George; Sharnoff, Joseph; Shultz, George; Silberman, Laurence H.; Sullivan, Warren; Thompson, Horace (Topper); Tobias, Paul H., 1930-; Truesdale, John C., 1921-2011; Usery, William J.; Weiss, Katherine Welder; Wirtz, Willard, 1912-2010; Zimny, Max; College of Labor and Employment Lawyers
6018721
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Tape 1 of 2. July 23, 2003. Camera A. Program time: 31 minutes, 23 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Tape 2 of 2. July 23, 2003. Camera A. Program time: 31 minutes, 59 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Tape 1 of 2. July 23, 2003. Camera B. Program time: 30 minutes, 59 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Tape 2 of 2. July 23, 2003. Camera B. Program time: 31 minutes, 50 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Howard Jenkins, interview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Tape 1 of 5. August 1, 2000.
- History of Labor Law: Howard Jenkins, Interview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Tape 2 of 5. August 1, 2000.
- History of Labor Law: Howard Jenkins, Interview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Tape 3 of 5. August 1, 2000.
- History of Labor Law: Howard Jenkins, Interview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Tape 4 of 5. August 1, 2000.
- History of Labor Law: Howard Jenkins, Interview, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Tape 5 of 5. August 1, 2000.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  B-Roll. Tape 1 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 33 minutes, 35 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Field Master original: Tape 2 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 31 minutes, 22 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Field Master Original: Tape 3 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 31 minutes, 22 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Field Master Original: Tape 4 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 29 minutes, 33 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Field Master Original: Tape 5 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 29 minutes, 30 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Field master Original: Tape 6 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 29 minutes, 38 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Field Master Original: Tape 7 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 29 minutes, 40 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Field Master Original: Tape 8 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 29 minutes, 52 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Field master Original: Tape 9 of 11. 19 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 31 minutes, 42 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Field Master Original: Tape 10 of 11. 19 and 20 October, 2001. Birmingham, AL. Program time: 28 minutes, 38 seconds.
- History of Labor Law: Judge U. W. Clemon, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  B-Roll. Tape 11 of 11. 20 October, 2001. Program time: 16 minutes, 53 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Judge U. W. Clemon Interview (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Tape 1 of 2. Total running time: 6 hours, 2 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Judge U. W. Clemon Interview (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Tape 2 of 2. Total running time: 6 hours, 2 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Tapes 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B. July 8, 2003.
- Labor Law Series: Howard Jenkins Interview (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Tape 1 of 1. Total running time: 3 hours, 3 minutes.
- Arvid Anderson, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  May 2006. Total running time: 46 minutes.
- Betty S. Murphy interviewed by John Higgins, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Samuel Pointer Interview, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Tape 1 of 1. October 21, 2003. Total running time: 2 hours, 40 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Tape 1 of 1. December 8, 2005. Switched version. Total running time: 1 hour, 46 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Tape 3 of 3. Total running time: 7 hours, 20 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Tape 2 of 3. Total running time: 7 hours, 20 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Tape 1 of 3. Total running time: 7 hours, 20 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  December 8, 2005. Isolated camera version. Total running time: 1 hour, 46 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Tape 1 of 1. June 1, 2005. Total running time: 5 hours, 58 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Tape 1 of 5. June 1, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Tape 2 of 5. June 1, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Tape 3 of 5. June 1, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Tape 4 of 5. June 1, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Tape 5 of 5. June 1, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: Honorable Samuel Pointer, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Tape 1 of 4. October 21, 2003.
- Labor Law Series: Honorable Samuel Pointer, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Tape 2 of 4. October 21, 2003.
- Labor Law Series: Honorable Samuel Pointer, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Tape 3 of 4. October 21, 2003.
- Labor Law Series: Honorable Samuel Pointer, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Tape 4 of 4. October 21, 2003.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias interviewed by Wayne Outten, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Tape 1 of 2. December 8, 2005. Program time: 1 hour, 31 minutes, 46 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias interviewed by Wayne Outten, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Tape 2 of 2 December 8, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias interviewed by Wayne Outten, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Tape 1 of 2. December 8, 2005. Switched version
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias interviewed by Wayne Outten, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Tape 2 of 2. December 8, 2005. Switched version. Program time: 1 hour, 14 minutes, 0 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Tape 1 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Tape 2 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Tape 3 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Tape 4 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Tape 5 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Tape 6 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Tape 7 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Tape 8 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Tape 9 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Tape 10 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Tape 11 of 11. October 21, 2004.
- Labor Law Series: Frances Bairstow, "Arbitrations" Fireside Chat, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  May 26, 2007.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Tape 1 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Tape 2 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Tape 3 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Tape 4 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Tape 5 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Tape 6 of 6. Total running time: 8 hours, 3 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Labor Law Series: Secretary Willard Wirtz Interview (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Tape 1 of 1. Total running time: 1 hour, 54 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Secretary Willard Wirtz Interview, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Tape 1 of 4. June 27, 2002.
- Labor Law Series: Secretary Willard Wirtz Interview, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Tape 2 of 4. June 27, 2002.
- Labor Law Series: Secretary Willard Wirtz Interview, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Tape 3 of 4. June 27, 2002.
- Labor Law Series: Secretary Willard Wirtz Interview, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Tape 4 of 4. June 27, 2002. Program time: 18 minutes, 54 seconds.
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Tape 10 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Tape 11 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Tape 2 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Tape 1 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Tape 9 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Tape 8 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Tape 7 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Tape 3 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Tape 4 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Tape 6 of 11
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Tape 5 of 11
- Labor Law Series: Frances Bairstow, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  May 26, 2007. Total running time: 1 hour, 12 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimny Interview (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Tape 1 of 3. Total running time: 3 hour, 10 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimny Interview (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Tape 2 of 3. Total running time: 3 hour, 10 minutes.
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimny Interview (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Tape 3 of 3. Total running time: 3 hour, 10 minutes.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Tape 1 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Tape 2 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Tape 3 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Tape 4 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Tape 5 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Tape 6 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Max Zimny Interview, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Tape 7 of 7. May 11. 2007.
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau interviewed by Richard Block, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Switched version #2. October 5, 2007.
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau interviewed by Richard Block, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Switched version #1. October 5, 2007.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Tape 5 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Tape 6 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Tape 2 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Tape 3 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Tape 1 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Tape 4 of 6. June 19, 2008.
- Marvin Miller, MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Tape 8 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Tape 7 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Tape 6 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Tape 5 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Tape 4 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Tape 3 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Tape 2 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- Marvin Miller: MLB, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Tape 1 of 8. June 6, 2008.
- CLEL Oral History: Deeds of Gift (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Arvid Anderson, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Summary and transcript. Fireside Chat, May 2006, interviewed by Joel Glanstein.
- Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Summary and transcript. Don Arthur Banta and Warren Sullivan discuss their careers from the 1950s to present, July 8, 2003.
- U. W. Clemon (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Transcript. Interviewed by William L. Robinson.
- Howard Jenkins, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Roberto L. Corrada.
- Theodore Kheel (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Bernard T. King.
- Digital copies of interview transcripts and summaries (Box 7)
  - Item 1: Edward Clair and Davitt McAteer on Mine Safety, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview summary. March 11, 2015.
    Format: Microsoft Word Doc.
  - Item 2: Edward Clair and Davitt McAteer on Mine Safety, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview transcript. March 11, 2015.
  - Item 3: William Brown, III, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview summary. Interviewed on September 29, 2015 by Patricia King.
  - Item 4: William Brown, III, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview transcript. Interviewed on September 29, 2015 by Patricia King.
  - Item 5: Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview summary. Interviewed on September 16, 2015 by William J. Kilberg.
  - Item 6: Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview transcript. Interviewed on September 16, 2015 by William J. Kilberg.
  - Item 7: Laurence H. Silberman, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Item 8: Laurence H. Silberman, 2015; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
  - Item 9: John E Higgins, Jr., 2016; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview summary. Interviewed on October 24, 2016 by Barry Kearney.
  - Item 10: John E. Higgins, Jr., 2016; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview transcript. Interviewed on October 24, 2016 by Barry Kearney.
  - Item 11: George P. Shultz, 2010; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview summary. Interviewed by William J. Kilberg, November 2, 2010.
  - Item 12: George p. Shultz, 2010; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Interview transcript. Interviewed by William J. Kilberg, November 2, 2010.
  - Item 13: ERISA Panel Discussion, 2012; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Panel discussion summary. Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 Panel consisting of Frank Cummings, Bob Nagle, Henry Rose, and Steve Sacher. Moderated by William J. Kilberg. April 2012.
  - Item 14: ERISA Panel Discussion, 2012; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Panel discussion transcript. Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 Panel consisting of Frank Cummings, Bob Nagle, Henry Rose, and Steve Sacher. Moderated by William J. Kilberg. April 2012.
  - Item 15: OSHRC Panel Discussion, 2011; Microsoft Word Doc (Box 7, Folder 0)
    Panel Discussion transcript. Occupational Health and Safety Review Commission panel consisting of Thomasina Rogers (then current Chairman), Scott Railton (past Chairman), Horace (Topper) Thompson (past Chairman), Don Elisburg, Ben Mintz, George Cohen, and Bob Gombar. With Cindy Atwood, George Salem, Randi Rabinowitz, Allen Sachsel, Rafael Moure- Eraso. June 21, 2011.
- George Nicolau, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Rich Bloch.
- Sam C. Pointer, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Charles A. Powell, III
- Paul Tobias, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Wayne Outten, December 8, 2005
- Willard Wirtz, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by N. Thompson Powers on June 27, 2002.
- Max Zimny (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Katherine Welderweiss.
- John Truesdale, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by John Higgins on June 1, 2005.
- John Higgins (Box 8, Folder 7)
- William Robinson Interview, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Interviewer: David Cashdan. Summary and transcript of interview DVD.
- James Harkless Interview, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Interviewer: Joseph Sharnoff. July 9, 2011
- Conversation between Edward Clair and Davitt McAteer concerning Mine Safety Law, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  March 11, 2015. Summary and Transcript
- Laurence H. Silberman, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Interview summary and transcript. Interviewed on September 16, 2015 by William J. Kilberg.
- Ruth Bader Ginsburg, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Interview summary and transcript. Interviewed on September 25, 2015 by William J. Kilberg.
- William H. Brown, III, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Interview summary and transcript. Interviewed on September 29, 2015 by Patricia King.
- John E. Higgins, Jr., 2016 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Interview summary and transcript. Interviewed on October 24, 2016 by Barry Kearney.
- George Shultz, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by William J. Kilberg, November 2, 2010.
- OSHRC Panel Discussion, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Transcript. Occupational Health and Safety Review Commission panel consisting of Thomasina Rogers (then current Chairman), Scott Railton (past Chairman), Horace (Topper) Thompson (past Chairman), Don Elisburg, Ben Mintz, George Cohen, and Bob Gombar. With Cindy Atwood, George Salem, Randi Rabinowitz, Allen Sachsel, Rafael Moure-Eraso. June 21, 2011.
- ERISA Panel Discussion, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Summary and transcript. Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974 Panel consisting of Frank Cummings, Bob Nagle, Henry Rose, and Steve Sacher. Moderated by William J. Kilberg. April 2012.
- U. W. Clemon Interview (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Transcript. Interviewed by William L. Robinson. No date. Tapes 2 and 3.
- William J. Usery Interview, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Les Hough on October 2-3, 2003.
- Marvin Miller Interview, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Gene Orza on June 6, 2008.
- Betty Murphy Interview, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by John Higgins on June 19, 2008.
- W. Willard Wirtz and William J. Usery Script, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Written and produced by Carol M. Rosenbaum. November 13, 2008.
- George Cohen Interview, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Mike Gottesman on June 28, 2012.